filetask.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy for File Task » FileTask

The importance of protecting user furnished, personally identifiable information is of the utmost concern to the owners of FileTask. The substance of this document describes the depth and measure of our policies concerning how we treat user furnished information. 

This is the complete Privacy Policy between you, the user of our website and/or software, and FileTask, the provider of this website and/or software. Read, with care, the full content of this Privacy Policy. 

Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect

During the process of dealing with FileTask, you may engage in one or all of the following acts of user registration: 1) Rights to access the FileTask website; 2) Software license and download applications; 3) Newsletter requests; 4) Other site specific but restricted access activities. Though the user information that we collect during these various registration processes may differ in scope and specifics, by and large we will be requesting the following personal and non-personal user data: 

1\. Legally given name;   
2\. Traceable physical address;   
3\. Variable email address;   
4\. Credit card numbers and/or other payment processing information;   
5\. Age;   
6\. Purposes for site access and/or software acquisition;   
7\. Other random, as necessary data. 

FileTask only gathers information that is related to the task at hand, and that can be clearly defined as necessary for adequate recording of any given transaction. FileTask always strives to ensure strict privacy controls and information security features. FileTask never knowingly collects personally identifiable information from minors. 

No user will be coerced into providing FileTask with user specific personally identifying information. However, failure to complete an associated registration process may limit your access to certain site features and to certain FileTask offered software packages. In the case of newsletter opt-in permissions and other user notification plans, every user is given the ability to opt-out at any time. 

Information Protection

FileTask values the trust of our users. We do not lease, loan, rent, sell, or trade your personally identifiable user information. Aside from the following three reasons, FileTask will never share your personally identifiable user information with a third party: 1) Specific and documented legal requirements; 2) Third party FileTask contract constrained service providers; 3) To protect our intellectual property rights. 

In the case of legally required information disclosure, FileTask will comply with the instructions of authorized authorities. 

As to sub-contracted service parties, FileTask ensures that these service agents implement and adopt a Privacy Policy that fully conforms to the constraints and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

When it comes to protecting our copyrighted intellectual property, FileTask will act as necessary to enforce the terms of our customer agreements. If you fail to comply with the terms of any FileTask originated EULA, Terms of Use Agreement, or Privacy Policy FileTask may disclose and/or user your personally identifiable information to involve applicable law enforcement agents. 

By submitting the information that we request, you agree to our personally identifiable user information collection, protection, and enforcement procedures. 

Random and Automated Information Collection

As a matter of practice, FileTask will collect user IP addresses and user website activity information. Additionally, FileTask makes a habit of installing and using computer cookies. We define computer cookies as various strings of data that are associated with our website through storage on a user\'s local computer system. These cookies enable us to identify specific computer systems and thereby provider quicker and more accurate customer services. Cookies also help us to protect our sales partners from purchase deceptions, and to protect ourselves from denial of service attacks upon our website. 

Information, Specific Usages

The information gathered in these manners permits FileTask to better evaluate the performance and goals of our website. The collected personally identifiable user information permits us to better manage our user accounts. 

Regardless of the means and the primary purpose for information of collection, any user data gathered by FileTask may be used and applied, but not limited to, the following purposes: 

1\. Customer account maintenance;   
2\. Product purchases and validations;   
3\. Website customizing;   
4\. Email and other forms of customer contact;   
5\. Information confirmation;   
6\. Notification of special advertising or product promotions;   
7\. Notification of changes to your rights concerning product or license terminations. 

Links

At times, of our choice, FileTask may host various onsite links to third party websites. This is not an endorsement of these linked sites. As such, these external websites are not under the authority of this Privacy Policy. Therefore FileTask makes no explicit declaration concerning the dependability or trustworthiness of linked sites. Any dealing that you may have with a linked site is your personal business and responsibility. 

Applicable Security Precautions

As a matter of primary concern, FileTask makes every effort to protect and secure your user furnished personally identifiable information. We maintain industry standard security measures throughout our offices and upon our equipment. Because security bleaches do happen, we cannot guarantee the total safety of your personally identifiable information. For this reason, we never retain user furnished personally identifiable information beyond a reasonable point transaction necessity. 

Policy Modifications and User Acceptance of Terms

As the creators of this Privacy Policy, FileTask retains the absolute right to update, replace, or terminate the entire contents of the agreement without respect to you the user. For your own knowledge, check back here often. 

By accessing, using, downloading, or otherwise acquiring materials that are offered by FileTask, you are acknowledging to the fullest extent that you agree with, and that you confirm to abide under, the information practices as described within this Privacy Policy.
